<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".WebScreen"
    android:orientation="vertical">

<TextView
    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    android:text="What is Web"
    android:textSize="25sp"
    android:textStyle="bold"
    android:layout_gravity="center"
    />

   <LinearLayout
       android:layout_width="match_parent"
       android:layout_height="wrap_content"
       android:gravity="center">

       <ImageView
           android:layout_width="300dp"
           android:layout_height="300dp"
           android:src="@drawable/www"/>


   </LinearLayout>
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        >



        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:text="World Wide Web, which is also known as a Web, is a collection of websites or web pages stored in web servers and connected to local computers through the internet. These websites contain text pages, digital images, audios, videos, etc. Users can access the content of these sites from any part of the world over the internet using their devices such as computers, laptops, cell phones, etc. The WWW, along with internet, enables the retrieval and display of text and media to your device.The building blocks of the Web are web pages which are formatted in HTML and connected by links called hypertext or hyperlinks and accessed by HTTP. These links are electronic connections that link related pieces of information so that users can access the desired information quickly. Hypertext offers the advantage to select a word or phrase from text and thus to access other pages that provide additional information related to that word or phrase.A web page is given an online address called a Uniform Resource Locator (URL). A particular collection of web pages that belong to a specific URL is called a website, e.g., www.facebook.com, www.google.com, etc. So, the World Wide Web is like a huge electronic book whose pages are stored on multiple servers across the world.Small websites store all of their WebPages on a single server, but big websites or organizations place their WebPages on different servers in different countries so that when users of a country search their site they could get the information quickly from the nearest server.So, the web provides a communication platform for users to retrieve and exchange information over the internet. Unlike a book, where we move from one page to another in a sequence, on World Wide Web we follow a web of hypertext links to visit a web page and from that web page to move to other web pages. You need a browser, which is installed on your computer, to access the Web."
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:gravity="center"/>
    </ScrollView>

</LinearLayout>